Guide to the Antiquarian bookseller catalog collection.
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- W
  - X346 W392, undated, 1963-1964; nos. 4-157, 5 catalogs
    - E. T. Webster; Suffolk (Box 1923, Folder 12212)
  - X346 W392 I, 1913-1935, undated; nos. 1-66, 8 catalogs
    - T. D. Webster; Kent, England (Box 1923, Folder 12213)
  - X346 W392 II, 1923 - 1938; nos. 1-66, 60 catalogs
    - D. Webster; Turnbridge Wells, England (Box 1924, Folder 12214-12219)
  - X346 W421, 1890 - 1937; nos. 1-225, 68 catalogs
    - Max Weg; Leipzig (Box 1925, Folder 12220-12230)
    - Max Weg; Leipzig (Box 1926, Folder 12231-12236)
    - Max Weg; Leipzig (Box 1927, Folder 12237-12240)
  - X346 W4214, 1906 - 1935; nos. 29-193, 67 catalogs
    - Oscar Wegelin; New York (Box 1927, Folder 12241-12245)
    - Oscar Wegelin; New York (Box 1928, Folder 12246)
  - X346 W427, 1892-[1939]; nos. 1-150, 59 catalogs
    - Adolf Wiegel; Leipzig (Box 1928, Folder 12247-12255)
    - Adolf Wiegel; Leipzig (Box 1929, Folder 12256-12261)
    - Adolf Wiegel; Leipzig (Box 1930, Folder 12262-12265)
  - X346 W427 II, 1903-[1939]; nos. 11/12-68, 28 catalogs
    "Mitteilungen für Bücherfreunde"
    - Adolf Wiegel; Leipzig (Box 1930, Folder 12266-12273)
    - Adolf Wiegel; Leipzig (Box 1931, Folder 12274-12275)
  - X346 W428, 1885-[1939]; nos. 2-179, 81 catalogs
    - Oswald Weigel's Antiquarium; Leipzig (Box 1931, Folder 12276-12283)
    - Oswald Weigel's Antiquarium; Leipzig (Box 1932, Folder 12284-12291)
    - Oswald Weigel's Antiquarium; Leipzig (Box 1933, Folder 12292-12295)
  - X346 W428 III, 1909 - 1933; nos. 10-144, 12 lists
    - Oswald Weigel; Leipzig (Box 1933, Folder 12296)
  - X346 W429, undated, 1866-1882, undated; nos. 1-32, 43 catalogs
    Includes six lists from another series
    - T.O. Weigel; Leipzig (Box 1933, Folder 12297-12298)
    - T.O. Weigel; Leipzig (Box 1934, Folder 12299-12305)
    - T.O. Weigel; Leipzig (Box 1935, Folder 12306-12310)
  - X346 W431, 1943-[ca. 1960]; nos. 1-33, 34 catalogs
    - E. Weil; London (Box 1935, Folder 12311-12312)
    - E. Weil; London (Box 1936, Folder 12313-12316)
  - X346 W433, 1964 - 1986; nos. 3-53, 18 catalogs
    - B. Weinreb Ltd.; London (Box 1936, Folder 12317-12319)
    - B. Weinreb Ltd.; London (Box 1937, Folder 12320-12324)
  - X346 W434, 1969; no. 7, 1 catalog
    - Beatrice C. Weinstock; Great Neck, N.Y. (Box 1937, Folder 12325)
  - X346 W435, [1938]; nos. 1-2, 2 catalogs
    - Julius Weises Hofbuchhandlung; Stuttgart (Box 1937, Folder 12326)
  - X346 W436, 1926; no. 11, 1 catalog
    - Weiss Co. Antiquariat; München (Box 1938, Folder 12327)
  - X346 W463, 1922 - 1942; nos. 2-51, 53 catalogs
    Includes four lists from another series
    - Edgar H. Wells Co.; New York (Box 1938, Folder 12328-12332)
    - Edgar H. Wells Co.; New York (Box 1939, Folder 12333-12338)
  - X346 W4875, [1957-1984]; nos. 136-310, 46 catalogs
    - H.Th. Wenner; Osnabrück (Box 1939, Folder 12339-12340)
    - H.Th. Wenner; Osnabrück (Box 1940, Folder 12341-12346)
    - H.Th. Wenner; Osnabrück (Box 1941, Folder 12347-12350)
  - X346 W4878, [1959]-1968; nos. 1-10, 13 catalogs
    Includes three catalogs from other series'
    - Henry W. Wenning Rare Books; New Haven, Conn. (Box 1941, Folder 12351-12352)
    - Henry W. Wenning Rare Books; New Haven, Conn. (Box 1942, Folder 12353-12355)
  - X346 W491, 1930 - 1956; nos. 8-183, 33 catalogs
    Includes several lists
    - B. Wepf Cie; Basel (Schweiz) (Box 1942, Folder 12356-12359)
    - B. Wepf Cie; Basel (Schweiz) (Box 1943, Folder 12360-12363)
  - X346 W521, 1935-[1942]; nos. 1-15, 9 catalogs
    - E.E. West; London (Box 1943, Folder 12364)
  - X346 W524, [ca. 1958]-1966; nos. 1-41, 38 catalogs
    - Herbert West, Bookseller; Hanover, New Hampshire (Box 1943, Folder 12365-12367)
    - Herbert West, Bookseller; Hanover, New Hampshire (Box 1944, Folder 12368-12371)
  - X346 W5248, 1967 - 1978; nos. 1-64, 13 catalogs
    - Western Hemisphere Inc.; Sharon, Mass. (Box 1944, Folder 12372-12374)
    - Western Hemisphere Inc.; Sharon, Mass. (Box 1945, Folder 12375-12376)
  - X346 W546, 1914 - 1977; nos. 5-114, 74 catalogs
    Name variant: The Weyhe Gallery. Location variant: London
    - E. Weyhe; New York (Box 1945, Folder 12377-12382)
    - E. Weyhe; New York (Box 1946, Folder 12383-12388)
    - E. Weyhe; New York (Box 1947, Folder 12389-12390)
  - X346 W546 I, [1920]-1948; unnumbered, 14 catalogs
    - E Weyhe; New York (Box 1947, Folder 12391-12392)
  - X346 W573, 1871 - 1891; unnumbered, nos. 77-127, 26 catalogs
    - John Wheldon; London (Box 1947, Folder 12393-12394)
    - John Wheldon; London (Box 1948, Folder 12395-12398)
  - X346 W573 II, 1901 - 1920; nos. 10-91, 44 catalogs
    "New series."
    - John Wheldon Co.; London (Box 1948, Folder 12399-12401)
    - John Wheldon Co.; London (Box 1949, Folder 12402-12406)
  - X346 W5735, 1931 - 1939; unnumbered, 43 lists
    - Wheldon Wesley Ltd.; London (Box 1949, Folder 12407)
  - X346 W5735 II, 1921 - 1986; nos. 1-172, 134 catalogs
    - Wheldon Wesley Ltd.; London (Box 1950, Folder 12408-12413)
    - Wheldon Wesley Ltd.; London (Box 1951, Folder 12414-12419)
    - Wheldon Wesley Ltd.; London (Box 1952, Folder 12420-12425)
    - Wheldon Wesley Ltd.; London (Box 1953, Folder 12426-12431)
    - Wheldon Wesley Ltd.; London (Box 1954, Folder 12432-12437)
    - Wheldon Wesley Ltd.; London (Box 1955, Folder 12438)
  - X346 W579, 1757 - 1765; unnumbered, 4 catalogs
    - John Whiston and Benj. White; London (Box 1955, Folder 12439-12443)
  - X346 W58, [1938-1939]; unnumbered, 2 catalogs
    - Whitcombe Tombs Ltd.; Auckland, Wellington (Box 1955, Folder 12444)
  - X346 W581, 1939; unnumbered, 1 catalog
    - Whitcombe Tombs Ltd.; Melbourne (Box 1955, Folder 12445)
  - X346 W582, 1785; unnumbered, 1 catalog
    - Benjamin White and Son; London (Box 1956, Folder 12446)
  - X346 W584, 1779 - 1784; unnumbered, 3 catalogs
    - Luke White; London (Box 1956, Folder 12447-12448)
  - X346 W587, 1816; unnumbered, 1 catalog
    - White, Cochrane, Co.; London (Box 1956, Folder 12449)
  - X346 W59, [1962-1986]; nos. 163-561, 132 catalogs
    - Whitlock Farm Booksellers; Bethany, Conn. (Box 1956, Folder 12450-12452)
    - Whitlock Farm Booksellers; Bethany, Conn. (Box 1957, Folder 12453-12458)
    - Whitlock Farm Booksellers; Bethany, Conn. (Box 1958, Folder 12459-12464)
    - Whitlock Farm Booksellers; Bethany, Conn. (Box 1959, Folder 12465-12470)
    - Whitlock Farm Booksellers; Bethany, Conn. (Box 1960, Folder 12471-12479)
  - X346 W59 I, [1973-1977]; nos. 9-18, 12 lists
    - Whitlock Farm Booksellers; Bethany, Conn. (Box 1960, Folder 12480)
    - Whitlock Farm Booksellers; Bethany, Conn. (Box 1961, Folder 12481-12484)
  - X346 W597, 1813 - 1816; unnumbered, 2 catalogs
    - Whitmore and Fenn; London (Box 1961, Folder 12485-12486)
  - X346 W649, [1946], undated; nos. 3-35, 7 lists
    - J. (Box 1961, Folder 12487)
  - X346 W65, 1760; unnumbered, 1 catalog
    - J. Wilkie; London (Box 1961, Folder 12488)
  - X346 W671, undated; unnumbered, 1 catalog
    - A. Williams Co.; Boston (Box 1961, Folder 12489)
  - X346 W673, 1946 - 1951; nos. 1-25, unnumbered, 32 catalogs
    - James A. Williams; Phila, Pa. (Box 1962, Folder 12490-12495)
  - X346 W6785, 1937 - 1955; nos. 11-99, 20 catalogs
    - G. Willis; London (Box 1963, Folder 12496-12498)
  - X346 W679, 1862; unnumbered, 1 catalog
    - Willis and Sotheran; London (Box 1963, Folder 12499)
  - X346 W686, [ca. 1941-ca. 1942]; nos. 1-14/15, 21 lists
    - Frank C. Willson; Melrose, Mass. (Box 1964, Folder 12500-12504)
  - X346 W691, [ca. 1949]-1953; nos. 1-27, 25 catalogs
    - Alfred Wilson; London (Box 1964, Folder 12505-12507)
  - X346 W6918, 1952-1957, undated; nos. 12-33, 8 catalogs
    - B. and L. Wilson Ltd.; London (Box 1964, Folder 12508)
  - X346 W692, 1949 - 1968; nos. 5-11, unnumbered, 10 catalogs
    - Bernard Wilson; London (Box 1964, Folder 10509)
    - Bernard Wilson; London (Box 1965, Folder 10510)
  - X346 W693, 1931 - 1940; nos. 33-48, 4 lists
    - H.W. Wilson Company; New York City (Box 1965, Folder 10511)
  - X346 W6942, 1905 - 1960; nos. 243-725, 139 catalogs
    Catalog 243 dates earlier than 1905, date portion of page [1] wanting
    - James Wilson; Birmingham (Box 1965, Folder 10512-12516)
    - James Wilson; Birmingham (Box 1966, Folder 12517-12522)
    - James Wilson; Birmingham (Box 1967, Folder 12523-12524)
  - X346 W6945, [1964-1968]; nos. 3-31, 17 catalogs
    - Jeff Wilson, Bookseller; Broomall, Pa. (Box 1967, Folder 12525-12526)
  - X346 W6947, 1971-[1986]; nos. 1-59, 31 lists
    - John Wilson; London (Box 1967, Folder 12527-12529)
    - John Wilson; London (Box 1968, Folder 12530-12532)
  - X346 W699, 1813; unnumbered, 1 catalog
    - Walter Wilson; London (Box 1968, Folder 12533)
  - X346 W722, [1921]; no. 2, 1 catalog
    - Fredk. C. Winchester; Sussex, England (Box 1968, Folder 12534)
  - X346 W734, 1900 - 1930; nos. 11-123, 49 catalogs
    - George Winter; London (Box 1968, Folder 12535-12537)
    - George Winter; London (Box 1969, Folder 12538-12539)
  - X346 W784, 1978 - 1982; nos. 8-16, 14 catalogs
    - Laurence Witten; Southport, Connecticut (Box 1969, Folder 12540-12543)
    - Laurence Witten; Southport, Connecticut (Box 1970, Folder 12544-12545)
  - X346 W7845, 1963 - 1966; nos. 218-251, 7 catalogs
    - Wittenborn and Company; New York, N. Y. (Box 1970, Folder 12546)
  - X346 W786, [1959]; nos. 3-49, 28 catalogs
    - Wittmann; Berlin (Box 1970, Folder 12547-12549)
    - Wittmann; Berlin (Box 1971, Folder 12550-12552)
  - X346 W832, [1958]-[1982]; nos. 1-45, 37 catalogs
    - William P. Wolfe Inc.; Pointe Claire, Quebec (Box 1971, Folder 12553-12554)
    - William P. Wolfe Inc.; Pointe Claire, Quebec (Box 1972, Folder 12555-12556)
  - X346 W833, [1938]; nos. 15-16, 2 catalogs
    - Hanns Wolff; Den Haag, Holland (Box 1972, Folder 12557)
  - X346 W842, 1936-1941, undated; unnumbered, 33 catalogs
    - Womrath; New York, N. Y. (Box 1972, Folder 12558-12559)
  - X346 W855, undated; nos. 1-59, 33 catalogs
    - Charles B. Wood III; South Woodstock, Connecticut (Box 1972, Folder 12560)
    - Charles B. Wood III; South Woodstock, Connecticut (Box 1973, Folder 12561-12565)
    - Charles B. Wood III; South Woodstock, Connecticut (Box 1974, Folder 12566-12568)
  - X346 W86, [1967]-[1969]; nos. 11-17, 6 catalogs
    - Jackson Woodruff; Point Richmond, California (Box 1974, Folder 12569)
  - X346 W871, 1876-[1902]; unnumbered, 17 catalogs
    - Charles L. Woodward; New York, N. Y. (Box 1974, Folder 12570)
    - Charles L. Woodward; New York, N. Y. (Box 1975, Folder 12571)
  - X346 W871 II, undated; nos. 2-50, 26 catalogs
    - Charles L. Woodward; New York, N. Y. (Box 1975, Folder 12572-12575)
  - X346 W8835, 1954 - 1956; nos. 4-10, 7 catalogs
    - Cecil Woolf; London (Box 1975, Folder 12576)
  - X346 W8855, 1963 - 1980; nos. 22-57, 26 catalogs
    - J. Howard Woolmer; Andes, N. Y. (Box 1976, Folder 12577-12579)
  - X346 W889 I, [1930]; nos. 1-69, 8 catalogs
    - Frank Woore; Nottingham (Box 1976, Folder 12580)
  - X346 W889 II, undated; nos. 11-59, 41 catalogs
    - Frank Woore; Derby (Box 1976, Folder 12581-12583)
    - Frank Woore; Derby (Box 1977, Folder 12584)
  - X346 W8948, [1951]-[1972], undated; nos. 238-272, 30 catalogs
    - Richard S. Wormser; Bethel, CT (Box 1977, Folder 12585-12588)
  - X346 W8948 I, [1932]; letters CO-Z, 16 lists
    - Richard S. Wormser; New York (Box 1978, Folder 12589-12590)
  - X346 W896, 1737; unnumbered, 1 catalog
    - John Worrall; London (Box 1978, Folder 12591)
  - X346 W925, 1938 - 1986; nos. 11-69, 48 catalogs
    - William P. Wreden; Palo Alto, California (Box 1978, Folder 12592-12594)
    - William P. Wreden; Palo Alto, California (Box 1979, Folder 12595-12599)
  - X346 W93, [1968], undated; nos. 6-40, 17 catalogs
    - Clark Wright; El Paso, Texas (Box 1979, Folder 12600)
  - X346 W933, 1914; no. 1, 1 catalog
    - J. Wright; Earlsfield, Surrey (Box 1980, Folder 12601)
  - X346 W934, 1905; unnumbered, 1 catalog
    - J. O. Wright Co.; New York, N. Y. (Box 1980, Folder 12602)
  - X346 W935, 1813; unnumbered, 1 catalog
    - P. Wright; London (Box 1980, Folder 12603)
  - X346 W938, undated; unnumbered, 1 catalog
    - Wrightson and Webb; Birmingham (Box 1980, Folder 12604)
  - X346 W9382, 1969 - 1970; nos. 1-19, 12 catalogs
    - John R. Wrigley; Chapeltown, Nr.Sheffield (Box 1980, Folder 12605-12607)
  - X346 W941, [1970]; no. 88, 1 catalog
    - Heinz Wunschmann; Berlin (Box 1980, Folder 12608)
- X
  - X346 X41, undated, [1967]-[1985]; nos. 1-72, 74 lists
    - Ximenes: Rare Books, Inc.; New York, N. Y. (Box 1981, Folder 12609-12613)
    - Ximenes: Rare Books, Inc.; New York, N. Y. (Box 1982, Folder 12614-12618)
    - Ximenes: Rare Books, Inc.; New York, N. Y. (Box 1983, Folder 12619-12621)
- Y
  - X346 Y12, undated, 1940-1968; nos. 3-47, 36 catalogs
    - Charles Yale; Pasadena, California (Box 1983, Folder 12622-12623)
    - Charles Yale; Pasadena, California (Box 1984, Folder 12624-12625)
  - X346 Y42, undated; nos. 9-19, 6 catalogs
    - Alan F. Yeoman; Tunbridge Wells, England (Box 1984, Folder 12626)
  - X346 Y42 II, 1929 - 1940; nos. 21-67, 45 catalogs
    - Alan F. Yeoman; Tunbridge Wells, England (Box 1984, Folder 12627-12628)
  - X346 Y85, 1882 - 1954; nos. 157-581, 168 catalogs
    Includes four unnumbered catalogs.
    - Henry Young Sons; Liverpool (Box 1984, Folder 12629)
    - Henry Young Sons; Liverpool (Box 1985, Folder 12630-12634)
    - Henry Young Sons; Liverpool (Box 1986, Folder 12635-12639)
    - Henry Young Sons; Liverpool (Box 1987, Folder 12640-12644)
  - X346 Y886, [1971-1972], undated; nos. 607-614, 3 catalogs
    - William Young and Co.; Winchester, Mass. (Box 1988, Folder 12645)
- Z
  - X346 Z11, [1921]; nos. 1-2, 2 catalogs
    - Zabala Maurin; New York, N. Y. (Box 1988, Folder 12646)
  - X346 Z165, 1896 - 1934; nos. 11-40, 20 catalogs
    - Zanichelli; Bologna (Box 1988, Folder 12647-12649)
  - X346 Z37, 1947; no. 65, 1 list
    - Zeitlin ver Brugge; Los Angeles, California (Box 1988, Folder 12650)
  - X346 Z37 I, 1965 - 1986; nos. 1-292, 77 catalogs
    - Zeitlin ver Brugge; Los Angeles, California (Box 1989, Folder 12651-12654)
    - Zeitlin ver Brugge; Los Angeles, California (Box 1990, Folder 12655-12659)
    - Zeitlin ver Brugge; Los Angeles, California (Box 1991, Folder 12660-12664)
    - Zeitlin ver Brugge; Los Angeles, California (Box 1992, Folder 12665-12669)
    - Zeitlin ver Brugge; Los Angeles, California (Box 1993, Folder 12670-12674)
    - Zeitlin ver Brugge; Los Angeles, California (Box 1994, Folder 12675)
  - X346 Z46, [1963]-[1969]; nos. 36-63, 17 catalogs
    Der Deutschen Demokratischen Republik
    - Zentralantiquariat; Leipzig (Box 1994, Folder 12676-12679)
    - Zentralantiquariat; Leipzig (Box 1995, Folder 12680-12683)
  - X346 Z627, undated; nos. 40-43, 4 catalogs
    - K. A. Ziegler; Zurich (Box 1995, Folder 12684)
  - X346 Z7, 1955 - 1967; nos. 4-40, 30 catalogs
    - Yanka Zlatin; Paris (Box 1995, Folder 12685-12687)
- Miscellaneous and Catalog Cards
  - X346 Misc, ca. 1963-ca. 1986; various numberings, 22 catalogs
    - Miscellaneous antiquarian bookseller catalogs. (Box 1996, Folder 12688-12702)
  - X346 Catalog cards, 7 boxes of cards
    Box 1998 includes catalog cards for antiquarian bookseller catalogs that have been discarded
    - Antiquarian bookseller catalog cards (Box 1997, Folder A-Q)
    - Antiquarian bookseller catalog cards (Box 1998, Folder R-Z)